[Music]
English listening test part three
designed for A2
learners. This test consists of 18
questions which are divided into three
parts. I will give you a short
instruction at the beginning of each
part. Before we get started, take a pen
and paper so you can take notes while
listening. Let's get started.
Part one, listen to a university teacher
giving instructions for an assignment to
practice and improve your listening
skills. For questions 1 to six, choose
the correct answer.
I want to explain a few things about
your essay. First of all, the deadline.
The deadline for this essay is October
18th. Not the 19th, not the 28th, not 2
days later because your cat was ill or
your computer broke. The 18th. If it's
late, I won't mark it. I won't even read
it. You'll fail the assignment, so
please hand it in on time. You can even
hand it in early if you like. You can
email me the essays at
m.steonnenlmu.ac us. That's s t e p p p
p p p p p p p p p p p p p p p p p p p p
p p p p p p p p p p p p p p p p p p h h
h h h h h h h h h h h h h h h h h h h h
h h h h h h h h h h h h h h h h h h e n
s o n. I'll reply to say I've got it. If
I don't reply within a day, it might
mean I didn't get it. So, please email
me again to make sure. You can also
bring a paper copy of the essay to my
office. But let's be kind to the trees,
okay? Email is better for the trees and
me. Don't forget that you must reference
every idea or quote you use that isn't
your idea. And the last page of your
essay should be a list of all the books
you used in alphabetical order, not in
the order you use them. And lastly, make
it easy for me to read. That means use a
clear font. Ariel is best, but Times New
Roman is fine, too. Not comic sands,
please. Size 12 font for the essay and a
size 14 font for the titles and
subheadings. And use page numbers. Any
questions?
[Music]
Part two. Listen to someone leaving a
message to practice and improve your
listening skills and be ready to choose
true and false questions.
Hello, this is the sales department
Rachel Fernandez speaking.
Hello. Is Maria Solomon there, please?
No, I'm sorry. She's not in the office
at the moment. She's on her lunch break.
Oh, could you take a message, please?
Could you tell her that Smith Griffin
called?
Sure. Could you give me your number?
It's 07460918.
Thanks. That's 0746029128.
Sorry, no, it's
0746099 0188.
99188.
Yes, please ask her to call me back and
tell her it's about the PXO project. I
need the new project figures.
The PXO
project? Right. I'll give her your
message when she comes back to the
office.
Thank you. In case I'm in a meeting,
when she calls back, can I give you my
email address, too?
Of course.
Great. It's smi
t. G r i ff i n at fsh.com.
Can I read that back to you?
Sure.
That's smi t.g r i f i n f resh.com.
Yes, that's it.
Okay, I'll tell her you called.
Thank you. Goodbye.
Goodbye.
[Music]
Part three. Listen to a student explain
why she can't come to class to practice
and improve your listening skills. For
questions 1 to six, choose the correct
answer.
Excuse me, Miss Johnson.
Yes, Selena. How can I help you? I'm
sorry, but I can't come to class next
Wednesday. I have a doctor's
appointment. Okay, thanks for letting me
know. Is there anything to do at
home? Let me just check my notebook.
Okay, first of all, you need to read
chapters 17, 19, and 20 in the book.
There are also some articles and a video
to watch. Those are online. I'll post
the links online in the usual place.
Chapters 17 to 20. Yes, except chapter
18, chapters 17, 19, and 20. Ah, okay.
Um, is there a deadline?
Yes, this Friday. But there's something
else. I was going to give you all a
practice test.
A practice test.
Yes. To help people prepare for the
midterm exam. Ah, all right. Don't
worry. I can send you the practice test
by email on Wednesday. Can you send it
to me before Friday? Sure. No
problem. And don't forget to bring a
certificate from the doctor to the
office. Thanks, Miss Johnson. I'll do
that. You're welcome, Selena. Take care.
[Music]
Don't forget to share your score in the
comment section. If you didn't watch the
second part of this level, you can find
the link in the
description. We will upload more
listening tests soon, so don't forget to
subscribe and stay tuned.
See you in our upcoming videos.
[Music]